Sourav Rajput Web designer

Souravrajput2503@gmail.com Souravrajput2503@gmail.com

4 9685578972

• Gurugram, Haryana

■ Indian

2002/03/25

in linkedin.com/in/souray-rajput-b610312a3

Professional Experience

2024/03 - present

WEB DESIGNER

Guragram, Haryana,

Design Creation Interior

India

2023/07 - 2024/01 Ahmedabad, India **WEB DESIGNER**

Tectonas Soft Solution

Professional Summary

Detail-oriented, analytical, and self-driven programmer with extensive experience building user-facing applications. Efficient and knowledgeable coder with skills in HTML, CSS, , and JavaScript programming languages. Coordinated and collaborative team player with attention to detail, Design skills, and ability to contribute to code base improvement initiatives and Ui improvement projects.

Skills

Photoshop	• • • •	Wireframe	• • • • •
Banner	• • • • •	Prototype	• • • • •
Crossbrower Compatibilities	• • • •	Content Optimization	• • • •
Code validation W3c	• • • • •	Html5	• • • •
CSS3	• • • •	GitHub	• • • •
WordPress	• • • •	Photoshop	• • • • •

Education

2020 - 2023	BACHELOR OF COMMERCE (B.COM)
	" " ' (MD)

Gwalior, India jiwaji university Gwalior, (M.P)

Courses

Gwalior, India WEB DESIGNER

ELIGHT CODING INSTITUTE

Projects

Blackwireless 2

Black011 🖸

MyMangoMobile 2

Interior-Construction

Siverce 🛮